THE NIGHT I
DIED, I GOT
A VOICEMAIL FROM
MYSELF TELLING ME
HOW TO HIDE.
I IGNORED IT.
SEVEN MINUTES LATER,
THE LOCKS ON
MY FRONT DOOR
CLICKED OPEN IN
THE EXACT SEQUENCE
THE VOICEMAIL PREDICTED.
NO FORCED ENTRY,
NO CODE KEYED
IN, BUT SOMEONE
WAS INSIDE.
THEY FOUND ME.
I WOKE UP
IN THE HOSPITAL.
MY PHONE WAS
CRACKED BUT STILL
ALIVE.
A NEW VOICEMAIL
FROM MY OWN
NUMBER. THAT WAS
A TEST.
TOMORROW AT 3
.15 YOU'LL GET
A CALL FROM
YOUR MOTHER'S OLD
NUMBER. SHE'S BEEN
DEAD TEN YEARS.
IT'S YOUR FUTURE
SELF. DO NOT
ANSWER IT. THE
PHONE RANG AT
3 .15.
I DIDN'T ANSWER.
IT WENT TO
VOICEMAIL. SILENCE.
THEN BREATHING.
THEN A WHISPER.
GOOD. YOU'RE LEARNING.
THE VOICE WAS
DEEPER.
EXHAUSTED.
TODAY YOU WILL
BUY A COFFEE
AT 4 P
.M. YOU WILL
MISS YOUR TRAIN.
DO NOT GET
ON THAT TRAIN.
I DIDN'T BUY
THE COFFEE. I
GOT ON THE
TRAIN.
I WAS GOING
TO BREAK THE
LOOP. THE TRAIN
DERAILED TWO STOPS
LATER. I WOKE
UP IN THE
SAME HOSPITAL ROOM.
SAME BANDAGES.
THE VOICEMAILS WERE
GONE.
A SINGLE TEXT
REMAINED.
YOU CAN'T SAVE
THEM IF YOU'RE
DEAD.
THE DOOR OPENED.
A NURSE SMILED.
MY PHONE BUZZED.
SHE'S NOT A
NURSE. I SAW
THE SYRINGE.
I ROLLED OFF
THE BED, CRASHED
THROUGH THE SECOND
STORY WINDOW AND
LANDED IN A
DUMPSTER. BROKE MY
RIBS.
THE LAST THING
I SAW BEFORE
I PASSED OUT
WAS MY PHONE
GLOWING IN THE
TRASH. A NEW
MESSAGE. SHE ISN'T
ALONE. START RUNNING.
I RAN FOR
A YEAR.
CHANGED MY NAME.
CHANGED MY FACE.
THE VOICEMAILS STOPPED.
THEN A POSTCARD
ARRIVED.
A COFFEE SHOP
IN PORTLAND.
A TIME.
8 A .M.
I KNEW I
SHOULDN'T GO. I
WENT ANYWAY.
A WOMAN WAS
WAITING BY THE
WINDOW.
SHE SMILED. THE
SAME SMILE FROM
THE HOSPITAL.
SHE SLID A
CASSETTE TAPE ACROSS
THE TABLE.
YOUR FATHER WANTED
YOU TO HAVE
THIS. HE KNEW
YOUR UNCLE KILLED
YOUR MOTHER.
HE KNEW YOUR
UNCLE WOULD TRY
TO KILL YOU,
TOO. I'M YOUR
SISTER, THE ONE
YOU DON'T REMEMBER
FROM THE FIRE.
I GOT THESE
SAME MESSAGES 30
YEARS AGO. MY
PHONE BUZZED. A
VOICEMAIL FROM 1987.
MY FATHER'S VOICE.
THE FIRE WASN'T
AN ACCIDENT.
BURN THE TAPE.
TRUST YOUR SISTER.
DON'T LOOK BACK.
I LOOKED UP.
SHE WAS GONE.
JUST THE TAPE
ON THE TABLE.
I FOUND A
LIGHTER IN MY
POCKET.
I HELD THE
TAPE OVER THE
FLAME.
AS THE PLASTIC
MELTED AND THE
RIBBON WARPED, I
HEARD MY OWN
VOICE, NOT FROM
MY PHONE.
FROM THE VERY
FIRST MESSAGE I
EVER GOT,
THE ONE I
DELETED,
NEVER HEARD THE
ENDING OF, I'VE
BEEN TRYING TO
WARN YOU FOR
30 YEARS MY
VOICE WHISPERED. YOU
CAN'T CHANGE IT.
YOU CAN'T SAVE
THEM. THE TAPE
BLACKENED AND DIED.
YOU JUST HAVE
TO LIVE IT.